Guide to the Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects, LLC, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project Records, 1965-2010
  - Quelle Farm, Main Residence
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1242)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1243, Box 1245, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1242, Box 1244)
  - Quelle Farm, Gate House, 1995
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1246)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1246)
  - Quelle Farm, Guesthouse, 1992
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1247)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1248)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1249)
  - Quelle Farm, Caretakers Residence/Garage, 1998
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1250–1251)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1250–1251)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1250)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1250)
  - Quelle Farm, SP4, 2009
    Job number: 20-0714
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1261–1264)
  - San Remo (Apartment 16 D/E), 1997
    Job number: 19-9404
    Client: Central Park West ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1181)
    - Correspondence (Box 1181)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1181, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1271)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1181, Box 1271, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1272)
  - Opel Residence, 1988
    Job number: 19-8513
    Job location: Sherbourne, VT
    Client: Opel
    - Correspondence (Box 1181)
    - Specifications (Box 1181)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1181, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1181, Box 1281, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1282–1283)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1284)
  - University of North Carolina at Charlotte, Thomas I. Storrs College of Architecture, 1987
    Job number: 19-8607
    Job location: Charlotte, NC
    Client: Univ. of North Carolina at Charlotte
    - Correspondence (Box 1161)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1161)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1292)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1291–1293, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1291)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1291)
  - Herman Miller Showroom, International Design Center, 1987
    Job number: 19-8621
    Client: Herman Miller
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1301–1302)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1301–1302, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1303)
  - The Georgetown Group, Inc. Offices, 1987
    Job number: 19-8704
    Client: The Georgetwon Group
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1311, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1311)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1311)
  - SBK Entertainment World Inc. Offices, 1988
    Job number: 19-8709
    Client: SBK Records Group
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1321, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1322–1323)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1324)
  - SBK EMI, 1991
    Job number: 19-8926
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1332)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1332)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1331)
  - McCann Erikson Worldwide Office, 1989
    Job number: 19-8716
    Client: McCann Erikson Worldwide
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1341–1343, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1343–1345)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1346)
  - Rosen Townhouses, 1993
    Job number: 19-8818
    Client: Rosen
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1351)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1351, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1351)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1352–1353)
  - Chen Residence, 1994
    Job number: 19-9018
    Job location: Taipei, Taiwan
    Client: Chen
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1361, Box 1363)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1361–1364, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1361, Box 1363–1364)
  - Ronald S. Lauder Corporate Offices, 1991
    Job number: 19-9020
    Client: Ronald S. Lauder
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1371)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1371)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1372)
  - RSL Foundation Offices, 1997
    Job number: 19-9616
    Client: Ronald S. Lauder Foundation
    - Design Development (Box 1161)
    - Correspondence (Box 1161)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1161)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1381)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1381, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1383)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1161, Box 1382)
  - PepsiCo World Headquarters, 1998
    Job number: 19-9104
    Client: PepsiCo
    - Background and Reports (Box 1391)
    - Correspondence (Box 1391)
    - Specifications (Box 1391)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1391, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1392–1395)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1391, Box 1395–1397, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1395–1398)
  - PepsiCo Leadership Conference Center, 1998
    Job number: 19-9603/9707
    - Background and Reports (Box 1391)
    - Design Development (Box 1391)
    - Correspondence (Box 1391)
    - Specifications (Box 1391)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1391, Box 1401, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1401)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1402)
  - PepsiCo Addition Bldg 4 Dining Facilities, 1998
    Job number: 19-9719
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1411–1412)
  - Sony Music Entertainment, Inc 550 Madison Avenue, 1996
    Job number: 19-9105
    Client: Sony Music Entertain-ment, Inc
    - Background and Reports (Box 1421)
    - Design Development (Box 1421)
    - Correspondence (Box 1421)
    - Specifications (Box 1421)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1428, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1422–1427)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1422–1423, Box 1427)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1421–1425, Box 1428)
  - Sony Music Entertainment, Inc 550 Madison Avenue, 1998
    Job number: 19-9114
    Client: Sony Plaza Public Arcade Sony Media World
    - Background and Reports (Box 1421)
    - Design Development (Box 1421)
    - Correspondence (Box 1421)
    - Specifications (Box 1421)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1431, Box 1433)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1421, Box 1434–1436)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1432, Box 1436)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1435)
  - Sony Music Entertainment, Inc 711 5th Ave 6th Floor, 1994
    Job number: 19-9324
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1441)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1442)
  - Sony Music Entertainment, Inc 550 Madison Avenue, 1996
    Job number: 19-9418
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1451)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1452–1453)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1451)
  - Stadtportalhauser Competition
    Job number: 19-9109
    Job location: Frankfurt-am-Main, Germany
    Project type: Competition
    Client: Stadtportal-hauser Competition
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1461–1462, Box 2074)
  - Master Plan, Broad College, Academic I, Student Activity Center Pitzer College, 1994
    Job number: 19-9113
    Job location: Claremont, CA
    Client: Pitzer College
    - Background and Reports (Box 1471)
    - Correspondence (Box 1471)
    - Specifications (Box 1471)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1471)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1472)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1471–1474, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1475–1477)
  - EMI Records Group Office Interiors, 1992
    Job number: 19-9205
    Client: EMI Records
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1481)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1482–1483, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1484–1485)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1482)
  - EMI Publishing, 1992
    Job number: 19-9206
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1486)
  - EMI Records, 1992
    Job number: 19-9207
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1487)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1487)
  - CitiCorp Center, Tower Plaza & Retail Atrium, 1995
    Job number: 19-9326
    Client: CitiCorp Center
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1491–1493)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1494–1495)
  - Pace Wildenstein Gallery, 1995
    Job number: 19-9416
    Project type: Cultural
    Client: Pace Gallery
    - Correspondence (Box 1391)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1501, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1501–1502)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1502–1503)
  - James S. McDonnell Hall of Physics, 1998
    Job number: 19-9509
    - Design Development (Box 1511)
    - Correspondence (Box 1511)
    - Specifications (Box 1511)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1511)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1512, Box 1516, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1514–1516)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1513, Box 1516)
  - The City University of New York, The Graduate Center, 1997
    Job number: 19-9521
    - Background and Reports (Box 1521)
    - Design Development (Box 1521)
    - Correspondence (Box 1521–1523)
    - Specifications (Box 1521–1523)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1521, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1524, Box 1539)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1521, Box 1525–1526, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1527–1528)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1529–1532)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1533–1538)
  - Pizzuti Residence, 2002
    Job number: 19-9609
    Job location: Columbus, OH
    Client: Pizzuti
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1541, Box 2075)
  - Belvedere Residence, 2003
    Job number: 19-9725
    Job location: Belvedere, CA
    Client: Belvedere
    - Background and Reports (Box 1511)
    - Correspondence (Box 1511)
    - Specifications (Box 1511)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1511)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1551–1552)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1511, Box 1551, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1552–1553)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1554–1556)
  - Ian Schrager Hotels Corporate Headquarters, 1998
    Job number: 19-9726
    Client: Ian Schrager Hotels Corporate Headquarters
    - Background and Reports (Box 1421)
    - Design Development (Box 1421)
    - Correspondence (Box 1421)
    - Specifications (Box 1421)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1421)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1561)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1562)
  - Miranova Suite 2600, 2000
    Job number: 19-9801
    Client: Miranova
    - Design Development (Box 1471)
    - Correspondence (Box 1471)
    - Specifications (Box 1471)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1571)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1572)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1573)
  - Central Park West Apartment (Apartment 19F), 2003
    Job number: 19-8919
    Client: CPW NYC Anonymous
    - Correspondence (Box 1161)
    - Specifications (Box 1161)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1581)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1581)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1161, Box 1582, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1584–1585)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1582–1583)
  - Daniels Lane Residence, 2003
    Job number: 20-0305
    Job location: Sagaponack, NY
    Client: Sagaponack ANONYMOUS
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1591–1592)
  - Oneonta Field House, 1996
    Job location: Oneonta, NY
    Client: State University Construction Fund: Oneonta
    - Background and Reports (Box 1601)
    - Correspondence (Box 1601)
    - Specifications (Box 1601)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1601, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1602–1603)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1601, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1603)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1604–1605)
  - Casa Vecchia (Bel Aire Residence), 2001
    Job number: 19-9617
    Job location: Bel Air, CA
    Client: Bel Aire ANONYMOUS
    - Design Development (Box 1611)
    - Correspondence (Box 1611)
    - Specifications (Box 1611)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1611, Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1612)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1612–1613, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1613–1616)
  - Ferris State University Library for Information, Technology and Education (FLITE)
    Job number: 19-9709
    Job location: Big Rapids, MI
    Client: Ferris State University
    - Background and Reports (Box 1621)
    - Design Development (Box 1621)
    - Correspondence (Box 1621–1622)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1621)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1623–1624)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1621–1624, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1625–1629)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1629)
  - Louise Wells Cameron Art Museum
    Job number: 19-9811
    Job location: Wilmington, NC
    Project type: Museum/Cultural
    Client: Cameron Art Museum
    - Background and Reports (Box 1631)
    - Design Development (Box 1631)
    - Correspondence (Box 1631)
    - Specifications (Box 1631)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1631)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1632)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1632, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1633–1636)
  - Akron Summit County Public Library (ASCPL)
    Job number: 19-9812
    Job location: Akron, OH
    Client: ASCPL
    - Background and Reports (Box 1641)
    - Correspondence (Box 1641)
    - Specifications (Box 1641)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1641)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1642)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1641, Box 1643–1644, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1643, Box 1645–1647)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1644)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Business Baker Library
    Job number: 19-9816
    Client: Harvard Graduate School of Business Baker Library
    - Design Development (Box 1651)
    - Correspondence (Box 1651)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1651, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1651)
  - Salt Lake City Library Competition
    Job number: 19-9901
    Job location: Salt Lake City, UT
    Client: Salt Lake City
    - Design Development (Box 1651)
    - Correspondence (Box 1651)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1651)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1651, Box 1661)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1651, Box 1661, Box 2076)
  - Bryant University, George E. Bello Center for IT
    Job number: 19-9903/0602
    Job location: Smithfield, RI
    Client: Bryant University
    - Background and Reports (Box 1671)
    - Correspondence (Box 1671)
    - Specifications (Box 1671)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1672–1674)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1671–1672, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1675–1678, Box 1680)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1678–1679)
  - Bryant University Interfaith Center
    Job number: 20-0602
    - Background and Reports (Box 1671)
    - Correspondence (Box 1671)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1691)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1692–1694)
  - Middlebury College Library & Starr Library
    Job number: 19-9904/0019
    Job location: Middlebury, VT
    Client: Middlebury College
    - Design Development (Box 1701)
    - Correspondence (Box 1701)
    - Specifications (Box 1701)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1701)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1701–1703, Box 1711)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1701, Box 1704, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1701)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1704, Box 1712–1715)
  - Denver Civic Center Competition
    Job number: 19-9919
    Job location: Denver, CO
    Client: Denver Civic Center
    - Design Development (Box 1721)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1721)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1721)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1721–1722)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1723)
  - Mid-Manhattan Library (Renovation + Expansion)
    Job number: 20-0001
    Client: New York Public Library Mid-Manhattan Library
    - Background and Reports (Box 1731)
    - Correspondence (Box 1731)
    - Specifications (Box 1731)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1732–1733)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1731, Box 1734–1735, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1734–1738)
  - SDI/Dell Gallery
    Job number: 19-9823
    Client: Austin ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1741)
    - Correspondence (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1741)
  - 6D Ranch Main Residence, 2007
    Job number: 20-0023
    - Background and Reports (Box 1741)
    - Correspondence (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1742)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1743)
  - 6D Ranch Lake House & Boat House, 2007
    Job number: 20-0032/0037
    - Background and Reports (Box 1741)
    - Correspondence (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1756)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1741, Box 1756)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1741, Box 1756)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1751–1754, Box 1757)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1755)
  - 6D Ranch Riding Complex, 2007
    Job number: 20-0038
    - Design Development (Box 1741)
    - Correspondence (Box 1741)
    - Specifications (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1761)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1762–1763)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1763)
  - 6D Ranch Mechanical Out Building, 2007
    Job number: 20-0041
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1771)
  - 6D Ranch Manager's House, 2007
    Job number: 20-0203
    - Correspondence (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1741)
  - 6D Ranch Pool House, 2007
    Job number: 20-0414
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1781)
  - 6D Ranch Sports Complex, 2007
    Job number: 20-0523
    Project type: Sports facility
    - Correspondence (Box 1741)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1791–1792)
  - Burchfield Penny Art Center (BPAC), 2008
    Job number: 20-0027
    Job location: Buffalo, NY
    Client: SUCF: State University College at Buffalo
    - Background and Reports (Box 1801)
    - Design Development (Box 1801)
    - Correspondence (Box 1801)
    - Specifications (Box 1801)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1801)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1802)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1801, Box 1803, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1804–1806)
  - Crocker Art Museum, 2010
    Job number: 20-0044
    Job location: Sacramento, CA
    Client: Crocker Art Museum Association (CAMA)
    - Background and Reports (Box 1811)
    - Design Development (Box 1811)
    - Correspondence (Box 1811–1812)
    - Specifications (Box 1812)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1811)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1811, Box 1813–1816, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1811, Box 1817–1818, Box 1827–1833)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1818–1822)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1822)
  - Apt 25 CPS, 2004
    Job number: 20-0103
    Client: Central Park South ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1841)
    - Correspondence (Box 1841)
    - Specifications (Box 1841)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1842)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1841, Box 1843, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1844)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1845)